Welcome to my YouTube channel Guys Hrithik
Technical Sup.  In this video we will
tell you how to get car insurance through Google Pay.
Because it is quite easy to setup.
If you have to take insurance etc. then
how will you do it?  We
will tell you in this video.  So first of all
I would like to tell you about an offer that
we have given you the link of
Google Pay in the description.  If you
create your account using that link, you will
get a referral bonus of ₹8,000 if you
make the first payment.  Ok?  Now
look, to get your car insurance,
you simply have to scroll down a bit.
Here you will get the View All feature,
you will have to click on it.  Then you
scroll down a little again.  We
will click on View All again and here it shows you
Finance and LIC Insurance in text.
Ok?  So simply you have to
click on this and select your
insurance provider.  Now see, Google
Pay does not have its own insurance company
but it suggests you from
where you can get insurance.
Like you can do with LIC of LIC.
You can take life insurance from SBI.
Extra from HDFC now depends on
whom you want to take it from.  For example,
I thought I have to get car insurance.
So you will see here that
you get a lot of options.  So
if I search here for a car, let's talk about a particular car,
here
we have car, that's it,
okay, HDFC Agro General Insurance Motor,
here you get to see motor
insurance, so if I talk about Ace General Motor Insurance, then
you will have to enter the policy number here, okay, enter
account details, then your registered
registration number, then your nick name, then
you have to continue, okay, now
enter here, for the first time when you
want to enter the policy number, then you can do it in this way
which is A B C D or you
can enter your number there later.  Ok?
Then you have to click on Continue.
After that you have to enter whatever your car number
is.  Now you can buy car insurance in this way
on Google Pay.  So,
see you in the next video